「復讐」
Vengeance...
Dammit!
くそっスカーだ
It was Scar!
マルコーが殲滅戦にかかわってたのを
He knew that Marcoh was involved in the extermination?!
知っていたのか
Can't focus. My body is still puzzled about what to do.
集中できてないな　まだ体が迷っているんだ
Shuuchuu dekitenaina mada karada ga mayotteirunda
I'm trembling. I can't stop even if I try to control myself.
震えていたんじゃ　コントロールしたってブレるんだ
Furueteitanja kontoroorushitatte burerunda
Although neither sun nor moon are on my side,
ツキ
太陽も勝負運もなんも完全にこっち向いていないが
Taiyou mo tsuki mo nanmo kanzen ni kocchi muiteinaiga
"I've no choice but to try,"
「やるしかないんだ」
Yarushikanainda
Those were the words I muttered to myself.
言い聞かせるようにそうつぶやいた
Iikikaseruyouni sotto tsubuyaita
The odds aren't on my side, but running way'd be gutless.
状況は悪いが　ただ逃げ出すんじゃ根性ないなぁ
Joukyou wa waruiga tada nigedasunja konjou nainaa
Even if I can't see the future, I'll just have to win it over with courage.
展望はないが　度胸でクリアするしかないや
Tenbou wa naiga dokyou de kuria suru shika naiya
Need to keep distance from the target as I hold myself back.
衝動は抑えたままターゲットとの間隔探れ
Shoudou wa osaetamama taagetto to no kankaku sagure
All that's needed for victory is pride to win.
必要なもんは勝つプライド
Hitsuyou na mon wa katsu puraido
Will we celebrate with the wine of victory
味わうのは勝利の美酒か
Ajiwau nowa shouri no bishu ka
Or'll we end up kissing their feet in defeat?
それとも敗北の苦汁か
Soretomo haiboku no kujuu ka
There are two outcomes to everything.
そう　すべては2つに1つ
Sou subete wa futatsu ni hitotsu
I want to control destiny.
操りたい運命の糸
Ayatsuritai unmei no ito
I need to seize the golden opportunity with my hands.
絶好のゴールデンタイム　この手で掴め
Zekkou no goorudentaimu kono te de tsukame
I'll finish it up with my best poker face,
渾身のポーカーフェイス　キメて仕掛けるよ
Konshin no pookaafeisu kimete shikakeruyo
And drag them into a world of illusions.
イリュージョンの世界へ引きずり込んで
Iryuujon no sekai e hikizurikonde
I'll find my way out of this endless pressure game,
際限無いプレッシャーゲーム　スルリと抜けて
Saigennai puresshaageemu sururito nukete
And leap over the borderline of honor.
栄光のボーダーライン　飛び越えるために
Eikou no boodaarain tobikoeru tameni
How many? What'll I need to sacrifice to make it happen?
ハウメニー？　どれくらいの代償がいる？
Haumenii? Dorekurai no daishou ga iru?
What is the one thing I don't want to let go?
手放したくないもんはどれ？
Tebanashitakunai mon wa dore?
新しい情報が入ったら教えるわ
I'll let you know when I get more information.
Isn't being an assistant to the Führer President the same thing as being taken hostage?
大総統補佐って人質みたいなもんだろ
大丈夫かよ
You sure you'll be okay?
前向きに考えるなら
To look at it in a positive light, it means I have the chance to assassinate him in his sleep.
隙あらば大総統の寝首をかけるってことよね
That's scary.
おっかねぇ
そうだ
Oh, right.
Do me a favor and let the Colonel know that Scar is still lurking around.
大佐に伝言
スカーがまだうろついてるって
分かったわ
Got it.
Lieutenant.
中尉
Yes?
何
Thanks for telling me about Ishbal.
イシュヴァールのこと
教えてくれてありがとう
アル
Al!
Brother! What's up?
兄さんどうしたの
Wow... So that's how things were in Ishbal...
そうなんだ
イシュヴァールでそんなことが…
She was willing to tell me everything, despite me being a kid.
オレみたいなガキに
全部話してくれたよ
錬金術師は真理を追い求める者
Alchemists are people who pursue the truth...
...and yet...
でも身近なことさえ分かってなかった
...we didn't even know about things so close to us.
So the Colonel is looking at the future that'll take place after he accomplishes his goal.
大佐は目的を果たしたその先を見てるんだね
The future that'll take place after he accomplishes his goal, huh...
目的を果たした先か…
Al, what do you plan to do after you get your body back?
アルお前元の体に戻れた後
何がしたい
Let's see...
そうだなぁまずは
For starters, I want to taste Winry's apple pie.
ウィンリィのアップルパイが食べたいかな
What about you, Brother?
兄さんは
元の体に戻るっつう目的で
I haven't really thought about it, since I've always been so intent on getting my limbs back.
いっぱいいっぱいだったからなぁ
とりあえず
I guess I'll start off by going around to Granny and Master and letting them know first.
ばっちゃんとか師匠に「戻りました」って
あいさつ回りかな
Yeah, they've really done a lot for us.
そっか
お世話になりまくりだもんね
みんな笑って迎えてくれるよね
They'll all greet us with smiles, right?
Yeah.
We'll be able to see their smiles, right?
みんなの笑顔見られるよね
Yeah.
We're in a tight spot, but that sort of cheered me up.
状況は厳しいけど
なんか元気出てきた
I've got something good to tell you, too.
明るい話もあるぜ
あのとき
We couldn't use alchemy at that time.
オレたちの術は発動しなかった
同じころ地上でも使えなくなってたらしいんだ
And it turns out others couldn't, either.
Then what about that girl and Scar...
じゃああの女の子とスカーは…
That's right. They were the only ones who could.
そうだ連中だけが使えた
何かあるんだ
There's something different about their alchemy...
あの二人の錬金術に
僕たちの知らない何かが…
Something we're not aware of...
Yeah.
We're not at a dead end yet.
まだまだどん詰まりじゃないぜ
出てったあの豆女が
Left?!
That midget left?!
Yeah. Early this morning.
今朝早くにな
Did she say where she was headed?!
でどこへ行くって
さあな
Nope.
ちっ捜すぞ
We've got to look for her!
セントラル中を手がかりもなしに
All of Central? Without a single lead?
手がかりならあるさ
We do have a lead.
なんだこりゃ
What's this?
A gift.
差し入れだ
In that case...
もっとこう…
おねえちゃんがいっぱい載ってる雑誌とかよぉ…
...couldn't you have brought me magazines with a lot of cute girls in 'em?
Don't be slacking off while we're gone, all right?
オレたちがいない間
サボるんじゃねぇぞ
もう行くのか
You're heading off already?
Yeah.
西部の名物料理でも食ってくるわ
I'm off to taste some western specialty dishes.
You'd better take care of this place while we're gone!
しっかり留守番してろよ
I will.
またな
Later.
ちゃんと食べて
Make sure you eat a lot and grow bigger and stronger.
強く大きくなれよ
留守の間みんなを守ってくれ
Protect everyone while I'm away.
フュリー曹長
Sergeant Fuery.
Hey.
Warrant Officer Falman!
ファルマン准尉
まだ出発してなかったんですか
You still haven't left yet?
I came to return something to the Colonel.
大佐に借り物を返しに来たんだよ
短いセントラル勤めだったなぁ…
It sure was a short stay in Central...
Were you transferred to Southern Headquarters, Sergeant?
曹長は南方司令部だっけ
Yes, sir. Opposite from you.
正反対ですね
I bet it's cold over in Northern Headquarters...
北方司令部って寒いんだろうなぁ…
じゃまたなフュリー曹長
Well then, so long, Sergeant Fuery.
Farewell. May we meet again.
はいまたお会いしましょう
失礼します大佐
Sorry to bother you, Colonel.
Lieutenant.
中尉
I came to pick up something I left here.
忘れ物を取りに来ました
そうか
I see.
スカーがまだうろついてるらしいですよ
Apparently, Scar is still lurking about.
Then I have to be extra careful.
それは気をつけなくてはいかんな
Since I no longer have a skilled bodyguard.
腕のいい護衛がいなくなることだし
死なないでくださいね
Please don't die.
Of course.
苦労をかけるな
Sorry to put you through so much trouble.
付く人を間違えたかもしれませんね
Perhaps I chose the wrong person to follow.
間違えたと思ったら撃ち殺せ
"If I ever stray away from my path, shoot me right away."
That was the deal.
あの日の約束だ
Your actions are still within the permissible range.
まだ許容範囲です
中尉は優しいな
You're too kind, Lieutenant.
So long, Colonel.
では大佐また
また
So long.
Please don't slack off, okay?
仕事サボらないでくださいね
Sure...
My pawn...
ポーンも…
いや趣味が高じてといいますか…
I guess my hobbies got the best of me...
My bishop...
ビショップも…
はっ光栄であります
Yes, sir! It is an honor!
My rook...
ルークも…
Thanks.
どうも
ナイトも…
My knight...
頭悪ぃから士官学校じゃ苦労しました
I'm stupid, so I had a rough time at the military academy.
そして…
And...
お望みとあらば地獄まで
If you wish, I'll follow you to the depths of Hell.
...even my queen was taken from me.
クイーンも取られた
But, it's too early...
がチェックメートには…
...for checkmate.
まだ早い
Like this! This is what the cat looks like.
これこういう猫
こいつを連れた小娘を捜してるんだ
I'm looking for a little girl carrying this thing around.
Sorry, please ignore that alien he's holding up.
すみません
あっちのエイリアンは無視してください
No one knows anything about that black and white cat...
白黒猫の情報なし…
I wonder if she left Central already?
もうセントラルにはいないのかなぁ
Fullmetal.
鋼の
大佐
Colonel!
なるほどシンの錬丹術か
I see. Eastern Alchemy from Xing, huh?
分かった
Got it.
I'll ask around about it, too.
ほかの者にも聞いておこう
本当は大佐に借りなんざ
To be honest, I didn't really want to ask you for any favors...
つくりたくねぇんだけどよ
Oh, yeah. Speaking of being in debt...
そうだ借りといえば…
...give me my money back.
金を返したまえ
Watch where you're going!
前見ろ前
覚えてやがったか…
So you remembered...
How much do I owe you again? 500 cenz?
いくらだっけ５００センズ
５２０センズだ
520 Cenz!
Don't try to play it off!
ごまかすな
んだよ細けぇな
What the hell! You're so stingy!
At this rate, you'll never make it big!
そんなこっちゃ大物になれねぇぞ
Sorry...
すみません…
Actually, I'm going to hold on to this.
やっぱまだ借りとく
大佐が大総統になったら返してやるよ
I'll return it when you become the Führer President.
Who told you?
誰に聞いた
Lieutenant Hawkeye.
ホークアイ中尉に
イシュヴァールのこともな
She told me about Ishbal, too.
Fullmetal.
鋼の
金は貸したままにしておく
You can keep the change for now,
必ず返してもらうぞ
but I'll be getting it back for sure.
んじゃ
When that time comes, I'll borrow money from you again.
そんときゃまた小銭借りるさ
「民主制になったら返してやる」ってな
With the promise "I'll give this back to you when you turn this country into a democracy".
And when you get that back, I'll borrow from you again and make you agree to something else.
それも返したらまた借りて
何か約束取りつけてやる
Which means I have a long life ahead of me, huh?
つまり私はかなり
長生きせねばならんということか
そうだよ中尉とかに心配掛けてんじゃねぇよ
That's right.
Quit worrying the Lieutenant!
Thanks for the ride!
送ってくれてどうもな
Later.
またな
遅かったな
You sure took a while.
I thought I'd be waiting here until I went bald.
待ちくたびれたぞ
Yo.
Oh, my! Roy!
あらロイさんお久ぁ
It's been so long!
You look well, Vanessa.
元気そうだねヴァネッサ
Long time no see, Roy.
久しぶりだねロイ坊
こんばんはマダム·クリスマス
Good evening, Madam Christmas.
How have you been?
元気だったかい
Not very well at all.
いや全然ダメ
景気づけに遊びに来た
I came here to liven up.
What can I start you out with?
何飲む
病み上がりなんでね
I'm actually recovering right now, so alcohol is a no-no.
酒はダメなんだ
特別なのを頼むよマダム
I'll be asking for the specialty, Madam.
あいよ
You got it.
Lieutenant General Grumman, you have a call from Central from a lady by the name of Madam Christmas.
グラマン閣下セントラルの
マダム·クリスマスという女性からお電話です
Oh?
Seriously... Please don't tell civilians about our secret line.
もう一般人に極秘回線を教えないでください
わしも捨てたもんじゃなかろう
It just means that I'm not completely useless.
この年寄りにご指名だよ
Someone has a task for this old geezer.
腕をなくし若を守りきれず
You lost your arm, failed to protect the young master,
and are now reduced to such a state...
この有様か…
Hey! What the hell are you doing?!
何すんだ
You still call yourself a chosen member of the Yao Clan?!
それでもヤオ家に選ばれし一族の者か
PLACEHOLDER
恥を知れ
Have some honor!
Cut it out, old man!
やめろじいさんケガ人だぞ
She's injured!
やめろって
I said stop!
ないのか…
Did you really lose it...
腕ないのか…
Did you really lose your arm...
ごめんなさい爺様
I'm sorry, Grandfather.
ごめんなさい…
I'm sorry...
Fool...
バカ者
バカ者…
Fool...
ランファンとの約束
As we promised, we'll set you up with an automail mechanic right away.
機械鎧技師を紹介しなきゃな
ダメだ
No.
お主らの好意だけ受け取っておく
Thank you for your consideration.
これ以上の助けはいらん
We shouldn't ask you to help us any further.
We'll somehow find an automail mechanic on our own.
機械鎧技師は我々でなんとかする
But we can't just leave you like this!
でもほっとけないですよ
敵にランファンの顔を見られている以上
Now that the enemy knows what Lan Fan looks like, we can't take any actions that may involve your friend in this.
お主らの知り合いを巻き込むわけにはいかん
分かったありがとう
Okay.
Thanks for the consideration.
あなたのお陰で孫娘が命を拾った
You saved my granddaughter's life.
感謝する
I thank you.
オレは人に礼を言われるような
I ain't a doctor that should be receiving gratitude-
医者じゃあ…
ノックス先生
Dr. Nox, thank you so much.
ありがとうございました
G-Get the hell out of here!
ととっとと出てけ
訳ありを長く置いておけるほど
I'm not kind enough to let you weirdos stay forever!
オレはお人よしじゃねぇんだよ
ったく
Seriously!
It seems the Emperor's condition is worsening by the day.
皇帝陛下の体調は悪化しているようだ
早く若を取り戻し不老不死の法とともに
We must get the young master back and return to our country with the stone as soon as possible.
国へ帰らねばのう
行くぞ
Let's go.
はい
Yes, sir.
Just wait, you fiends.
待っていろ魔窟の住人どもよ
我々はまた戻ってくる
We shall be back soon.
助けていただいたご恩は忘れません
I'll never forget my gratitude to you for saving me.
Dr. Nox, thank you so much.
ノックス先生ありがとうございました
今更医者面かよこのオレが
And now  I'm starting to act like a doctor after all this?
はいよどなた
One sec.
Who is it?
Oh.
こんばんは父さん久しぶり
Hey, Dad.
It's been so long.
Are you doing okay?
あなた元気
Of course.
近くに寄る用事があったから…
We had some business around here, so...
You've gotten taller.
でかくなったな
お前やせたんじゃないか
Don't you think you've lost some weight?
You're one to talk.
あなたこそ
Is your work keeping you busy?
仕事忙しいの
Yeah, I've been performing on corpses as always-
相変わらず死体の相手…
あっ いや
Well, wait.
I treated two live patients this week.
今週は生きた患者を２人ほど治療したな
Isn't that funny?
笑えるよな
このオレが人命救助だとよ
Me, saving people's lives?
父さんオレ
Dad, I'm studying to become a doctor.
医者を目指してるんだ
父さんがイシュヴァール以来
I know that you've been going through a rough time ever since you returned from Ishbal.
ずっと苦しんできたのは知ってる
Yet, you didn't quit your job.
それでも父さんは
医者をやめようとはしなかった
オレは医者である父さんが好きなんだ
I love you, Dad! As the doctor you are and have always been.
Idiot...
バカ野郎が…
Why don't you come in?
上がれよ
The coffee's not too tasty, but have a cup or two.
あんまりうまかねぇけどよ
コーヒーでも飲んでけ
Wow, it's such a mess in here!
散らかってるな
Come, let's get this place cleaned up while Dad makes us coffee.
さっお父さんがコーヒーいれてくれてる間に
片づけましょう
もしも神様ってのがいるなら
God, if you really do exist, please overlook this.
見逃してくれよ
こんなオレでもよ
Even someone like me can enjoy a cup of coffee with his family, right?
家族とコーヒー飲むぐらいの幸せは
願っていいよな
これでイシュヴァールは
And with this, Ishbal has completely fallen under the control of the army.
完全に国軍の管轄に入った
Well done, Major Kimblee.
ご苦労だったなキンブリー少佐
How do you like the philosopher's stone?
どうだ賢者の石は
It's wonderful.
すばらしいです
等価交換を無視して
I was able to perform transmutations beyond my dreams while ignoring the concept of equivalent exchange.
予想以上の錬成を行えましたよ
よろしい
Good.
Make a record of the details and submit it.
詳細を文書にして提出したまえ
Now give us the stone back.
石は返してもらおう
何をするキンブリー
What have you done, Kimblee?!
さてこれで賢者の石の在りかを知るのは
Now, it's only you all who know where the stone is.
あなた方だけですね
貴様
You bastard!
What the hell?!
なんだ
何があった
What happened?!
どうした
What was that?!
Whoops.
おっと
出ろキンブリー釈放だ
Come out, Kimblee. You're being released.
どういうことですか
What's this about?
余計なことは聞くな
You don't need to know.
上からの命令ですか
Is it an order from the higher-ups?
うるせぇよ
Shut up.
Besides, why weren't you put on
death row after killing five officers?
だいたいなんで士官５人殺して
死刑になってないんだよお前
どんな手使った
What trick did you use?
いえ何も
Nothing in particular.
Maybe it's because of my natural virtues?
人徳じゃないですか
Don't make me laugh, you bomberman!
笑わせんな爆弾狂が
こんなイカれたヤツを釈放するなんて
What the hell are the higher-ups thinking, releasing a freak like you?
何考えてんだお偉いさんは
看守さん
Mr. Jailer, thanks for taking care of me for all this time.
長い間お世話になりました
Don't come back again.
もう戻ってくるなよ
ほんのお礼です
Just a token of my gratitude.
Don't tell me...
まさかちょっと待て
Wait!
Stop! Please, take it off!
やめろ外してくれ
Kimblee!!!
キンブリー
It's a boring old toy.
つまらないオモチャです
お子様にでもあげてください
Please give it to your kid or something.
Well then, farewell.
ではさようなら
Now...
さてと…
It's been a while, Kimblee.
久しぶりだねキンブリー
出所おめでとう
Congratulations on your release.
So it was you all who let me out.
あなたたちの命令でしたか
Yup.
そっ人手が足りないんでね
We've run into a labor shortage.
ということは仕事を下さると
Which means, you have a job for me?
ドクター·マルコーを覚えてるかい
Do you happen to remember Doctor Marcoh?
The scientist who helped create the philosopher's stone, right?
賢者の石を作っていた研究者ですね
よく覚えていますよ
I remember him very clearly.
そのマルコーが逃げた…
He may...
かもしれない
...have escaped.
"May have"?
かも
まだはっきりしてないんだよ
It's still not clear yet.
One of the chimeras we placed as a watchdog was gone.
番犬代わりに置いといた合成獣が
一頭いなくなっていた
マルコーは生体錬成に秀でた錬金術師だ
Marcoh is an alchemist especially skilled in organic transmutation.
The corpse may have been a substitute.
あれは身代わりかもしれない
And to make matters worse,
そして厄介なことに
スカーと呼ばれるイシュヴァール人と
there's a possibility he's on the run with Scar, an Ishbalan.
逃げてる可能性がある
So, how does that sound to you...
どうだい
...as someone who was ordered to annihilate Ishbal, the Crimson Alchemist?
イシュヴァール殲滅を命じられた
紅蓮の錬金術師としては
Let's see...
そうですね
自分が取りこぼしたイシュヴァール人だとしたら
If it's an Ishbalan that I forgot to kill, then it's hard to let this one pass.
許し難いことです
You're allowed to kill Scar on sight.
スカーは見つけたら殺していい
だけどマルコーは連れてこい
But bring Marcoh back alive.
それだけのために私を
You released me from jail for something like that?
Once we capture Marcoh, we're going to wipe a town off the map just to show him who he's messing with.
マルコーを捕まえたら
見せしめに町を一つ
地図から消してやるんだ
いい仕事だろう
Isn't that a pleasant job?
You're really a nasty person, aren't you?
えげつないことしますねぇ
久しぶりに使えますね
I can finally use this, after all this time.
That may not be enough if we're
planning to destroy an entire town.
町一つ消すんなら
それじゃ足りないかもよ
Wow...
これは…
Did you make this out of Ishbalans, too?
またイシュヴァール人を使って
It's made out of the guys who were researching the stone under Doctor Marcoh.
ドクター·マルコーの部下で
石の研究をしてたヤツらだよ
You truly are nasty.
ほんとにえげつない
Why did you help me escape?
なぜ私を逃がした 私は…
I...
There are still things I need to ask you.
貴様には
まだ聞かねばならんことがある
キンブリーという錬金術師のこと
About the alchemist named Kimblee, and...
それと
...there were parts I couldn't understand in the research documents my brother left me.
兄が残した研究書に
オレでは理解できん部分があった
研究書
Research documents?
兄は死ぬ前に
"There's something strange about this country's alchemy" are the words he left me before he died.
「この国の錬金術はおかしい」と言っていた
そのことが書かれているはずだ
Something about that should be written in the documents.
貴様はやり手の錬金術師
You're a skilled alchemist.
解読できるな
You'll be able to comprehend it, won't you?
この国の錬金術がおかしい
Something strange about this country's alchemy?
だんな
Master. The little girl came back.
あの娘戻ってきましたぜ
スカーさんご無事でしたか
Mister Scar! You were okay!
あれっ
Huh? We have another friend with us?
お仲間さんが増えました
He's not a friend.
仲間ではない
His name is Marcoh.
名はマルコー
He's a man who created a philosopher's stone and assisted in the Ishbalan Extermination.
賢者の石を作り
イシュヴァール殲滅に加担した男だ
賢者の石って不老不死の
A philosopher's stone! For immortality?!
Mister Marcoh, do you know how to make the stone?!
マルコーさん石の作り方を
知っているんですか
どうやって教えてください
How?! Please, tell me!
Well, that's...
いやそれは…
よせ
Stop.
そんなもの求めるな
You shouldn't wish for such a thing.
I only destroyed the exterior of his face.
顔の表面だけ破壊した
こいつの血を止めてやってくれ
Please stop his bleeding.
えっはい
Okay!
It's better to destroy his face so others won't be able to tell who he really is.
顔は本人だと分からぬくらい
（大丈夫ですかマルコーさん）
Are you okay, Mister Marcoh?
崩れていた方が都合がいい
Let's go.
出発するぞ
Huh? To where?
どちらへ
オレが兄から受け継いだ研究書を隠した場所
To the place I hid the documents.
North.
北だ
Even if we part and meet again, I want to meet at this place.
巡り巡ってもまたここで逢いたい
Megurimeguttemo mata koko de aitai
Then we'll hold hands to ensure we'll never be separated again.
はぐれないようにこの手をつなぐんだ
Hagurenaiyouni kono te wo tsunagunda
We used to talk all night until the sun rose,
朝日が昇るまで語り合ったね
Asahi ga noboru made katariattane
And held hands till the sun went under the horizon.
夕陽が沈むまでつないだ手
Yuuhi ga shizumu made tsunaida te
Let's walk together like this forever, like light and shadow.
こうやって明日も明後日も共に歩もう光と影
Kouyatte asu mo asatte mo tomo ni ayumou hikari to kage
I stand in the city, staring off into space with lonely eyes.
寂しげに見つめる街の中で
Samishige ni mitsumeru machi no naka de
I can't find warmth on my own.
温もりはひとりじゃ見つからなくて
Nukumori wa hitori ja mitsukaranakute
By meeting you, I realized
愛がこんなに強さになること
Ai ga konnani tsuyosa ni narukoto
How much strength love could give me.
知ったんだ　キミに出逢えてはじめて
Shittanda kimi ni deaete hajimete
Even if we part and meet again, I want to meet at this place.
巡り巡ってもまたここで逢いたい
Megurimeguttemo mata koko de aitai
Then we'll hold hands to ensure we'll never be separated again.
はぐれないようにこの手をつなぐんだ
Hagurenaiyouni kono te wo tsunagunda
I can't sleep by myself, 'cause I can't dream without you.
一人じゃ眠れない　夢は見れないから
Hitori ja nemurenai yume wa mirenaikara
So take me to a place where uncertainty can't reach us
どんな不安も届かないところへ
Donna fuan mo todokanai tokoro e
And let us bring light to the night sky with no stars.
星のない夜も照らし続けよう
Hoshi no yoru mo terashitsuzukeyou
So long as you're with me, I can go to world's end.
何処までも行けるキミとなら
Doko made mo yukeru kimi to nara
Even if it's a path I can't walk on my own,
一人じゃ歩けない道も二人なら
Hitori ja arukenai michi mo futari nara
If you're by my side, I can walk it while humming a tune.
鼻歌歌いながら歩けるんだ
Hanauta utainagara arukerunda
If we're together, the world is mine.
キミがいれば幸せ
Kimi ga ireba shiawase
日本語字幕仕上げ：XIAOBIN
隠れていた姿は
The figure hidden all this time reveals himself with a smile.
ほほ笑みとともに現れ
漫遊字幕組
http://popgo.net/bbs
新たな火種が
With that, a new threat endangers the tangled web Central is.
錯綜するセントラルに降りかかる
次回　鋼の錬金術師
Next time, Fullmetal Alchemist:
FULLMETALALCHEMIST
Episode 32, The Führer's Son.
第３２話 「大総統の息子」
知らない方が幸せか
Would it be better to not know?
それとも…
Or perhaps...